<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

 <title>ProUtils Ruby Blog</title>
 <link href="http://proutils.github.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
 <link href="http://proutils.github.com/"/>
 <updated></updated>
 <id>http://proutils.github.com/</id>

 
 <entry>
   <title>The History of Detroit</title>
   <link href="blog/2011-06-24-history-of-detroit/index.html"/>
   <updated>2011-06-24</updated>
   <id>proutils.github.com</id>
   <content type="html">
    <p>Detroit, which until recently was called "Syckle", has been through a number major redesigns.</p>

<p>Detroit has it's origins in Reap</p>

<p>The first version of was essentially what Hoe is today albiet with fewer tasks. Likely to the dismay of
any early followers of the project, the second version warped into a Rake clone. Seeing no point to a slighly
improved rewrite of Rake, the third version made a complete u-turn and had every task as a separate script
utilizing a special DSL. Each task script could also call on other scripts simply by name (via
method_missing). This design was very interesting, but was lacking in certain respects (largely in maturity),
so the penultimate version evolved these tasks into a set of stand-alone executables patterned after git's
"many small commands" design. This worked well, but it proved difficult to learn the proper usage and sequence
of usage of so many tools. This natually led to the current version whereby all tasks belong to a life-cycle,
similar to Maven. The user triggers a cycle-phase and all prior phases are run through until the requested
cycle-phase is reached.</p>

    <br/><br/>
    [<a href="blog/2011-06-24-history-of-detroit/index.html">Read More</a>]
   </content>
 </entry>
 
 <entry>
   <title>New Website</title>
   <link href="blog/2011-06-23-welcome-to-detroit/index.html"/>
   <updated>2009-07-30</updated>
   <id>proutils.github.com</id>
   <content type="html">
    <p>Okay so we tried the Jekyll --the static site generator supported by GitHub.
Jekyll is a good static site generator with nice blogging features. I give it
a lot of credit. But I have taken a stab at a static site generator myself more
than a few times and with some inspiration from Jekyll I fianlly was able
create a system that is worth the effort to code.
I dubbed it <i>Brite</i> (short for We<b>b</b> W<b>rite</b>).</p>

<p>While there are still some features to add, this site demonstrates the fruit
of my labor. I won't terry on with the details here. You can read them on
the <a href="http://proutils.github.com/brite">Brite</a> website. But I will at least say,
for the first time I am fully satisfied with with a static site generator,
enough so to use it for all my future project sites.</p>

    <br/><br/>
    [<a href="blog/2011-06-23-welcome-to-detroit/index.html">Read More</a>]
   </content>
 </entry>
 

</feed>